Filip Popescu Front End Developer

💌 philpopescu@gmail.com 📞 514-567-4095 💡 Montreal, Canada 👩 fpops.github.io/portfolio

нтмі

CSS

React Tailwind

Python

Javascript

₽ PROFILE

I am a self-taught Front End developer, specializing in creating beautiful and engaging websites. Comfortable working with HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, and Bootstrap. Great at working with a team as well as just by myself. Always interested in gaining further experience and learning new technologies.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web developer

Freelance

May 2022 - present | Montreal, Canada

- Create product cards with vanilla HTML and CSS
- Made a one-page reactive page with Bootstrap
- Created an expense chart component with vanilla JS

Photographer

Freelance

June 2021 - present | Montreal, Canada

- Engaged with clients during shoots to create a comfortable atmosphere and enjoyable experience
- Used both digital and film cameras to create beautiful street and landscape photography
- Edited the pictures with Adobe Photoshop and Lightroom

Product Specialist

September 2019 - March 2020 | Laval, Canada

- Responsible for handling customer questions and complaints, processing sales
- Provided excellent customer service and resolved conflict effectively

Sales

Econofitenss

May 2016 - August 2019 | Dorval, Canada

- Handled customer transactions and customer support
- Maintained gym equipment in perfect working order
- Showed patrons the proper way to use the different machines for their workouts

Survey

Kiewit

May 2015 - September 2015 | Pointe du Bois, Canada

- Responsible for mapping and recording material placements
- Ensured each layer of material placed followed the project specifications (height, width)
- Added measurements to the site database for analysis and archiving

⊗ SKILLS

EDUCATION

(Cert) Computers and Information Technology

McGill University January 2021 - May 2023 Montreal, Canada

BSc Physics

University of Montreal 2016 - May 2020 | Montreal, Canada

♦ LANGUAGES	
English	
French	
Romanian	

聞 COURSES

CS50's Web Programming with Python and JavaScript

Harvard

June 2022 – present | Boston, USA

JavaScript Algorithms and Data **Structures**

FreeCodeCamp June 2022 - July 2022 Montreal, Canada